http://www.howardcenter.org/privacy-policy

Chichewa
Chinese (Simplified)
Chinese (Traditional)
Korean
Kurdish (Kurmanji)
Mongolian
Myanmar (Burmese)
Home
Howard Center is open and serving our community. Main Number: 802-488-6000; First Call for Chittenden County 802-488-7777. If you experience longer than a 15 minute wait for a call back, please call again. We continue providing some services via telephone and video telehealth. The Resource Center and Onion River Program at Knight Lane in Williston remain closed temporarily.
Howard Center is Open.
CLOSE X
MENUMENUDevelopmental Services
Developmental Services
Getting StartedI Need Help Now
Developmental Services
What to Expect When I Call
Am I Eligible for Services?
Client Handbook
How We HelpCounseling
Education
Vocational & Employment
Flexible Family Funding
Home & Housing Supports
After High School & Community Support
Communication Support
What to Expect When I Call
Am I Eligible for Services?
Client Handbook
How We HelpCounseling
Educational Programs
Vocational & Employment
Home & Housing Supports
Community Support Programs
Additional Resources
Who We HelpChildren & Youth
What to Expect When I Call
Am I Eligible for Services?
Client Handbook
How We HelpOpiate Use & Medication Assisted Treatment
Impaired Driver Rehabilitation Program
Alcohol & Other Substances
Counseling
Education
Syringe Exchange and Overdose Prevention
Home & Housing Supports
Careers
Call now.
We’ll answer your questions and help you get started.
Howard Center Main Number
802-488-6000
CRISIS: Need Help Now?
802-488-7777
Howard Center Website Privacy Policy
(This policy is specific to the Howard Center website, www.howardcenter.org,  and posted on it).
The privacy of our customers is important to Howard Center. We understand that visitors to Howard Center’s website need to be in control of their personal information. You do not have to give us personal information to visit our sites. If you choose not to provide personal information, you can still visit all Howard Center webpages. Therefore, the following is Howard Center’s Website Privacy Policy:
Cookies
What is a cookie?
A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser — along with a Web page — when you access a Web site. There are two kinds of cookies. A session cookie is a line of text that is stored temporarily in your computer’s memory. Because a session cookie is never written to a drive, it is destroyed as soon as you close your browser. A persistent cookie is a more permanent line of text that gets saved by your browser to a file on your hard drive.
Howard Center does not use any cookies.
Data Collection
We may collect personally identifiable information (name, e-mail address, physical address, and other unique identifier) only if specifically and knowingly provided by you.
Information collected is for statistical purposes only. Howard Center performs analyses of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various areas of our sites.
Howard Center also uses listservs to send out information and change notices to subscribed users of our sites.
Howard Center will protect the personal information that you share with us. Howard Center does not disclose, give, sell, or transfer any personal information to third parties. If we share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only.
E-Mail
While Howard Center will make every attempt to protect the personal information that you share with us, electronic mail is not secure against interception. If your communication is very sensitive, you may want to send it by encrypted email or postal mail instead.
We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifiable information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information
